docclub.com 2014-11-27

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

Welcome to Doc Club. This is the privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") for www.docclub.com (the "Site"). The Site is provided by Digital Store LLC and its affiliates ("Doc Club", "we", "our" or "us").  Please review our Terms of Use Agreement which governs your use of the Site. Any capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning ascribed in the Terms of Use Agreement. 

This Privacy Policy will remain in full force and effect, even if your use of or participation in the Site or any particular service, feature, function or promotional activity offered on or in connection with the Site terminates, expires, ceases, is suspended or deactivated for any reason. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not participate in the Site or any features, activities or services offered on or in connection with the Site which require your personal information. 

This Privacy Policy applies regardless of the Device you use to access the Site and whether you are accessing the Site as a registered user (i.e., an end user with a User Account) or otherwise.  This Privacy Policy governs only the Information (as defined herein) collected by us on or in connection with the Site and does not cover any other information collected in any other manner or collected by any other entity, unless specifically stated. Where you have provided your personal information to third parties such as affiliated companies, marketing companies or Advertisers and have provided sufficient consent, we may obtain such personal information and combine it with your Information and, if we do so, our use of the resulting combined Information will be subject to this Privacy Policy. 

You may choose to provide certain information to us when you use the Site. When we use the term "Personal Information" we mean any information that we collect on or in connection with the Site that would allow someone to identify you or contact you, such as your full name, address, e-mail address, payment card information or telephone number. When we use the term "Additional Information", we mean any information that we collect on the Site other than Personal Information. (Personal Information and Additional Information shall be collectively referred to as "Information"). By visiting, accessing or otherwise using the Site, you affirmatively consent to our collection and use of Information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

#### 1\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT 

A.         **User Registration.** If you elect to become a registered user of the Site, we will require you to provide as part of your User Account certain Information, which may include, but not be limited to, your email address, legal name, etc., and, in order to conduct fee-based transactions, your physical address, telephone number(s), applicable payment data (e.g., credit card number and expiration date), etc. and your date of birth, country of residence, zip code, etc. 

B.         **Site Features, Functions and Communications.** The Site may provide you with access to certain features or functions, such as interactive and community features, message boards, ratings and profile pages which may be subject to Additional Terms including notices and settings which will determine who can see such information which you should read before adding your Information to the feature and using it. To participate in these features and functions, you may be asked to provide certain Information about you in order to personalize and/or allow you to use these features and functions. For example, in order to personalize your user profile on the Site, you may have the option to provide certain additional information, including, but not limited to, your city, state and country, a short description of yourself, a profile image, or other information and content. At times, you may be presented with the opportunity to sign up to receive newsletters, email communications, or other communications from us in order for us to provide up-to-date information about the Site, and to publicize and promote certain content, products and services offered by us or our business partners. When there is a separate sign-up for newsletters, we may ask for your contact information such as name and email address, and, sometimes, demographic and profile information.  We may ask you to confirm your consent to these uses at the time you sign up for these services or communications. 

C.         **Promotions, Contests, and Sweepstakes.**   To participate in certain Promotions, including contests, sweepstakes and surveys, there may be a separate registration process which may require the submission of both Personal Information and Additional Information (including, but not limited to, your full name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, demographic or profile information, etc.). We will use the Information you provide for the purpose of conducting the promotion, including, without limitation, contacting you if you have won. You may also have the opportunity to opt-in to receive special Promotions or offers from our Advertisers as a result of your use of the Site and such activity may be governed in accordance with Section 4 herein. 

D.         **Information Collected Through Automatic Data Collection.  ** Our Site includes features that automatically collect your Internet protocol (IP) address and Additional Information regarding your visits to the Site to assist us in keeping track of your preferences, create a more tailored user experience and better serve your particular interests and needs. 

The Site and/or third parties may use "cookies," (which are small data files containing information about you that is stored on your hard drive), "embedded scripts", and other similar tracking technologies (collectively, "Tracking Technologies") to collect Additional Information automatically as you interact with the Site. Some cookies are used to make login to our Site easier (such as by remembering your User Account).  Cookies also enable us to track your interaction with the Site and target your interests to enhance your Site experience. We may also use Tracking Technologies to collect "clickstream" data, such as the domain name of the service providing you with Internet access, the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your browser type and version, operating system and platform, the average time spent on our Site, pages viewed, content searched for, access times and other relevant statistics, and assign unique identifiers to the Device you use to access the Site for the same purposes. We may associate the information obtained through these Tracking Technologies with your Personal Information so we can better customize your Site experience and provide tailored advertisements and Promotions related to your specific interests.  By visiting the Site, whether as a registered user or otherwise, you acknowledge, understand and hereby agree that you are giving us your consent to track your activities and your use of the Site as described in this Privacy Policy. 

This Site may also use a variety of third party advertising networks, data exchanges, traffic measurement service providers, marketing analytics service providers and other third parties (collectively, "Third Party Advertising Service Providers") to, for example, serve advertisements on the Site, facilitate targeting of advertisements and/or measure and analyze advertising effectiveness and/or traffic on the Site. Such services may enable us to display advertisements based on your visits to the Site and other websites you have visited. Targeting services enable us to, among other things, help deliver advertisements or other content to you for products and services that you might be interested in, to prevent you from seeing the same advertisements too many times and to conduct research regarding the usefulness of certain advertisements to you. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies.  Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer.  For example, if you are using Internet Explorer, search for "Cookies" in the Help menu to find detailed instructions.  If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to use interactive features of this Site or other Web sites that depend on cookies. 

#### 2\. HOW WE USE INFORMATION 

  * We may use your Personal Information for the following purposes:
  * Providing any services or products that you request or purchase through the Site; 
  * Contacting you regarding the administration of any features or functions of the Site; 
  * Sending you marketing and promotional e-mails and correspondence; 
  * Allowing you to participate in the community and other features of the Site; 
  * Responding to your questions or other requests; 
  * Tailoring your experience on the Site and/or otherwise customizing what you see when you visit the Site; 
  * Saving your User Account or other Personal Information (so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit the Site); 
  * Providing you with a website and services of enhanced value to you; 
  * Marketing and promoting the Site and services, including Promotions and other initiatives and activities; 
  * Where you order goods or services, performing credit checking where relevant.  Please note that when a credit reference agency receives a search from us they will place a footprint on your credit file that may be seen by other organizations; 
  * For the prevention and detection of fraud or infringement of our or our licensor’s rights 
  * Tracking your return visits to the Site; 
  * To comply with legal obligations or legal process; and 
  * For other purposes disclosed at the time you provide us with the Personal Information or which are reasonably necessary to provide the service requested. 

In addition, we may use the Additional Information for many purposes, including, without limitation, the following:

  * For research purposes, for marketing/promotional purposes and/or to provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients; 
  * Accumulating and reporting aggregate, statistical information in connection with the Site and user activity; 
  * Determining which features and services users like best to help us operate the Site, enhance and improve our services and the Site and display advertising and marketing information; 
  * Saving certain Additional Information for use on your return visits to the Site; 
  * For the uses described for "Personal Information" above; and 
  * For other purposes disclosed at the time you provide us with the Additional Information or which are reasonably necessary to provide the service requested. 

####  3\. OPTING-OUT OF CERTAIN USES OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AND OTHER INFORMATION 

A.         **Marketing and Promotional Communications.  ** At times, you may be presented with the option of whether to receive certain marketing and promotional communications from us and others that we think will be of interest to you. Recipients who have consented to receive such communications can unsubscribe by either following the specific instructions included in such communications or you may "opt-out" of receiving marketing and promotional e-mails from us at any time by changing your account settings on the Site or by sending an email to us at support@docclub.com detailing your privacy request. Please note that "opt-out" and "unsubscribe" requests may not take effect immediately and may take a reasonable amount of time to receive, process and apply, during which time your Information shall remain subject to the prior privacy settings. Additionally, you should be aware that any Information provided to third parties prior to your election to opt out or unsubscribe cannot be retrieved or rescinded by Doc Club unless required by applicable law, and you cannot retroactively opt out or unsubscribe with respect to such third parties.  Further, also please note that in order to keep you informed about the operation of our Site and related services, we may always send you emails and announcements that are needed for the proper functioning and administration of our Site, including for the purposes described in Section 2above, in connection with your use of the Site. We may also have features that allow you to submit information, questions or feedback to us. In those instances, we may retain your emails and other information you submit to us for our internal purposes, and to help us and our Site service providers serve you better. 

B.         **Other Uses.** Please see Section 5 below in relation to the withdrawal of consent for other uses. 

####  4\. SHARING AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION AND OTHER INFORMATION 

A.         **General Disclosure.  ** Generally, we do not sell, rent, lease or disclose your Personal Information to third parties, except if you consent to such disclosure or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.  We reserve the right to use and/or sell any anonymous aggregated data we collect in connection with your use of the Site, including for the purposes described in Section 2 above. Our affiliated companies, including all of their respective business units, subsidiaries, parents, affiliates and sites may obtain from us and be able to use your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  You can choose to opt-out of certain such uses as described in Section 3 above. We may share Additional Information with third parties, but we do not disclose Personal Information to them except as described in this Privacy Policy. 

B.         **Co-Branded Services, Features and Promotions.**  The Site may offer co-branded services and features, such as events and Promotions provided by us and/or our affiliated companies or other third party partners, and that may be hosted on the Site and/or our co-branded partner's website. We may share your Personal Information with such co-branded partners and your voluntary use of or participation in a co-branded service or feature means that you hereby opt-in and give your affirmative consent to both the Site and our co-branded partners to collect any information provided in connection with the specific co-branded feature or service and to use such information for the fulfillment of the feature or service and for marketing or administrative purposes in accordance with our respective privacy policies. The co-branded partner will be identified on the co-branded feature or service, along with the co-branded partner's privacy policy. If you wish to opt-out of a co-branded partner's future use of your Personal Information for marketing or other purposes, you will need to contact the co-branded partner directly.  Please note that the use of such information by co-branded partner is subject to co-branded partner's privacy policy. 

C.         **Disclosure of Certain Information in User Postings Intended to Be Disclosed.** Certain Personal Information associated with a User Posting may be intended for disclosure, such as your username. We will disclose any such Personal Information in connection with the display of, and other services relating to, such User Posting and by submitting a User Posting on our Site you affirmatively consent to the distribution of your Personal Information as described herein. 

D.         **Site Service Providers.  ** We also have the right to disclose your Personal Information and other information to third parties and affiliates for the purpose of administering and maintaining the Site's services, features, functions and operations. We will refer to these parties in this context as "Site service providers".  We use Site service providers to efficiently provide the full range of content, activities, services, features and functions we bring you and we disclose your Information to Site service providers for the purpose of providing services to us. These Site service providers may temporarily store some information on their servers, but they may only use your Personal Information to provide Doc Club with a specific service and not for any other purpose and agree to keep such Personal Information secure and confidential. 

E.         **Additional Disclosures.**  There may be instances when Doc Club may access or disclose Information without providing you a choice in the following circumstances: (a) to protect or defend the legal rights or property of Doc Club, our affiliated companies or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements); (b) to protect the safety and security of our Site and users; (c) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; (d) if we believe your actions violate the Terms of Use Agreement, this Privacy Policy, any Rules and/or Additional Terms; or (e) to comply with law or legal process. In addition, if Doc Club sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of all or a material part of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, Doc Club may transfer your Personal Information to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction who may use that Information for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. 

#### 5\. USER CHOICE, WITHDRAWAL OF CONSENT AND ACCESS 

By using the Site (a) and providing us with your contact information, you expressly choose to receive certain communications from us and, unless you otherwise indicate, certain third parties as described in this Privacy Policy, and (b) you expressly agree to the privacy practices described herein. You may change your privacy preferences (e.g., choose to cease receiving certain communications or ask us not to share your Personal Information with a particular third party) by sending an email to us at support@docclub.com detailing your privacy request. Other privacy preferences (e.g., deactivating your user account) may be made by modifying your account settings on the Site. Except as described in this Privacy Policy, Doc Club will get your permission before we use the Personal Information you provide to us in a way that is inconsistent with the purpose for which it was submitted or share your Personal Information with third parties that are not affiliated with Doc Club.  If you ask Doc Club to stop using your Personal Information, we will honor that request while retaining a record of any Personal Information as necessary to comply with applicable federal, state or local law. However, you may be unable to continue to use a product or service or that product, service or the features on the site may be impaired or disabled if you require us to stop using your Personal Information. You always have the right to access and correct the Personal Information you have provided and generally you may review, update or delete certain Information collected by the Site at any time by accessing your account as described in this Section 5 or by contacting us as described in Section 12. 

#### 6\. DATA COLLECTION FROM CHILDREN 

We do not knowingly collect personal information from individuals under the age of 18. Please visit http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/edu/pubs/consumer/tech/tec08.shtm for information from the Federal Trade Commission about protecting children's privacy online.  

#### 7\. SECURITY 

While no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure from intrusion, we maintain commercially reasonable physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your Personal Information. However, regardless of our efforts and the Device you use to access the Site, it is possible that third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications over an unsecured transmission. We also limit access to the Site by our own employees, contractors, Site service providers and those individuals who are authorized for the proper handling of such information. We request that our third party contractors and Site service providers follow similar standards of security and confidentiality.  

#### 8\. YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS 

If you are a resident of the State of California, we provide you with information on how to exercise your disclosure choice options such as your right to opt-out (which we may sometimes refer to as "unsubscribe") or opt-in for use of your Personal Information by third parties (such as Advertisers) for marketing purposes. Therefore, pursuant to the California Civil Code, we are not required to maintain or disclose a list of the third parties that received your Personal Information for marketing purposes during the preceding year.  If you are a California resident and wish to request information about how to exercise your third party disclosure choices, please send a request by email to our Privacy Administrator at support@docclub.com or by postal mail to Doc Club, Digital Store LLC, c/o Privacy Administrator, 11 Penn Plaza, New York, NY 10001, Attn: Your California Privacy Rights.   

All requests must be labeled "Your California Privacy Rights" on the email subject line or envelope or post card. For all requests, please clearly state that the request is related to "Your California Privacy Rights", include your name, street address, city, state, zip code and e-mail address (your street address is optional if you wish to receive a response to your request via email) and indicate your preference on how our response to your request should be sent (email or postal mail). We will not accept requests via the telephone or by fax. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information. 

#### 9\. LINKS 

The Site may be linked to Internet sites operated by other companies. The Site may also feature advertisements from other third parties. Doc Club is not responsible for the privacy practices of such websites or other services operated by third parties that are linked to or integrated with the Site or for the privacy practices of third party Internet advertising companies. Once you leave this Site via such a link, access a third party application (such as widgets, APIs, etc.) or click on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party site to determine, among other things, how they will handle any personally identifiable or other information that they may collect from you. 

#### 10\. PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES 

From time to time we may modify this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives or changes in the law, our Information collection and use practices, the features of the Site, or technology, and such modifications shall be effective upon posting. Your continued use of the Site after we post a revised Privacy Policy signifies your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy.  It is therefore important that you review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure you are updated as to any changes.  If we materially change our practices regarding collection, use or disclosure of your Personal Information, your Personal Information will continue to be governed by the Policy under which it was collected unless you have been provided notice of, and have not objected to, the change. 

#### 11\. ACCURACY 

It is your responsibility to give us current, complete, truthful and accurate information, including Personal Information, and to keep such information up to date. We cannot and will not be responsible for any problems or liability that may arise if you do not give us accurate, truthful or complete information or Personal Information or you fail to update such information or Personal Information. We will reject and delete any entry that we believe in good faith to be false, fraudulent or inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. 

#### 12\. INTERNATIONAL VISITORS 

The Site is controlled, operated and administered entirely within the United States. If you visit the Site from a location outside the United States, please be advised that any Information you provide may be processed in and transferred to the United States or other non European Economic Area countries, where privacy protections may not be as comprehensive as those in the European Union or other territories and locations.  However, we will only process your Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. By using this Site, you affirmatively consent to this transfer and to the use of your Information as described herein. 

#### 13\. CONTACT US 

If you have any questions about our privacy practices or any of the terms or conditions of this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at:  Email:   [support@docclub.com](mailto:support@docclub.com)

OR

Mail:  
**Doc Club**  
_Digital Store LLC_  
Attn: Privacy Matters 

11 Penn Plaza   
New York, NY 10001  

#### 14\. SOLE STATEMENT 

This document is the sole statement of the Site's Privacy Policy and no summary, restatement or other version thereof, or other privacy statement or policy, in any form, including, without limitation, machine-generated, is valid. 

This Privacy Policy was last modified on the date indicated above and is effective immediately. Copyright © 2010 Digital Store LLC
